R breathe
in
At my table there is no place for anyone, It's a fight for who is, stay with me, I want to be with my brothers,
To break all the money, to sing only for us, for all the people.
At my table there is no place for anyone, It's a fight for who is, stay with me, I want to be with my brothers.
We are the best organized brigade, No one will ever pass over us,
It would be good to know, to be happy, To stand in your bank and not to make a mistake.
I want to be with my brothers, To break all the money, to sing only for us, for all the people.
At my table there is no place for anyone, It's a fight for who is, stay with me, I want to be with my brothers,
To break all the money, to sing only for us, for all the people.
I want to be with my brothers, To break all the money, to sing only for us, for all the people.
At my table there is no place for anyone, It's a fight for who is, stay with me, I want to be with my brothers,
To break all the money, to sing only for us, for all the people.
We are the best organized brigade, No one will ever pass over us,
It would be good to know, to be happy, To stand in your bank and not to make a mistake.
I want to be with my brothers, to break all the money, for all the people.